Brazilians certainly know how to throw a party – but will Rio be ready to welcome over 10,000 athletes and all the international visitors to the 2016 Olympics?
巴西人当然知道如何举办派对——但里约热内卢准备好迎接超过1万名运动员以及所有来参加2016年奥运会的国际游客了吗？
At the moment, some natives of Rio (known locally as 'Cariocas') aren't too enthusiastic about the Games.
目前，一些里约热内卢的当地人（在当地被称为“卡里奥卡人”）对奥运会并不是太热情。
They know they'll be putting up with a lot more roadworks and infrastructure building before the Olympic torch is lit in the Maracanã Stadium next August.
他们知道，在明年8月奥运火炬在马拉卡纳体育场点燃之前，他们将不得不忍受更多的道路施工和基础设施建设。
Delays in venue construction gave the International Olympic Committee a fright in 2014.
2014年，场馆建设的延迟吓了国际奥林匹克委员会一跳。
The government has since cleaned up its act and was praised recently for being ''on the right track'', although the challenge of cleaning up the highly polluted waters of the Rodrigo de Freitas Lagoon and Guanabara Bay – venues for the sailing and rowing competitions – remains.
自那以后，政府已经整改了自己的行为，并且最近因“走在正确的轨道上”而受到赞扬，不过，清理罗德里戈・德弗雷塔斯泻湖和瓜纳巴拉湾（帆船和赛艇比赛的举办场地）受到严重污染的水域这一挑战仍然存在。
Fortunately, Brazil has learnt a lot from hosting the World Cup in 2014.
幸运的是，巴西从2014年举办世界杯的经历中学到了很多。
Some businesses realised they were missing a trick by not communicating well with their international customers.
一些企业意识到，由于没有与国际客户进行良好的沟通，他们没有抓住一些行业诀窍。
Restaurants now know that using the internet to translate the menu isn't always a good idea: 'bife a cavalo' isn't really 'horse steak' – it's beef with a fried egg on top!
现在餐馆也知道，用互联网翻译菜单并不总是个好主意：“bife a cavalo”并不是真正的“马排”——而是上面放有一个煎蛋的牛肉！
Security was a key challenge in 2014 – and during the Olympics, the police will be working hard to prevent street crime.
2014年，安全是一个关键挑战——在奥运会期间，警方将努力预防街头犯罪。
As with other developing countries, crime rates are high, and visitors will be encouraged to keep their wits about them so as to avoid falling victim to pickpockets or muggers.
正如其他发展中国家，巴西的犯罪率很高，游客将被鼓励保持机智警觉，以便避免成为扒手或抢劫犯的受害者。
So while the Cariocas are already becoming athletes – by jumping and running across construction sites on their daily commute – they know that the Games have the potential to be a great spectacle, they will be able to let their hair down, and international visitors will have a good time in their company.
所以，虽然卡里奥卡人已经在成为“运动员”了——因为他们在日常通勤时要跳过和跑过建筑工地——但他们知道奥运会有可能成为一场盛大的奇观，他们将能够尽情放松，国际游客也会在他们的陪伴下玩得很开心。
Even those Brazilians who have their reservations, know deep down something that others don't.
即使是那些持保留意见的巴西人，在内心深处也知道一些别人不知道的事情。
An old local saying goes: 'Deus é Brasileiro' ('God is Brazilian').
当地有一句古老的谚语：“Deus é Brasileiro”（“上帝是巴西人”）。
They hope he will give them a hand to make the games a success.
他们希望上帝能帮他们一把，让奥运会取得成功。
And you can be sure that whatever happens – or doesn't happen – Brazilians will show the world why they have such a reputation as party people!
而且你可以肯定的是，无论发生什么——或者不发生什么——巴西人都会向世界展示为什么他们会有善于举办派对的名声！